<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Projects on Jacob Biehler</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Jacob Biehler</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 22:09:12 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://biehlerj.xyz/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cointop</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/projects/cointop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 22:09:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://biehlerj.xyz/projects/cointop/</guid><description>Cointop is a CLI utility written in Go to track cryptocurrencies.
My contribution to Cointop was to make sure that the configuration file was read from and added to the user&amp;rsquo;s declared config directory otherwise it would use a standardized path.
The previous behavior would override the user&amp;rsquo;s config directory. For instance on Linux if you had $XDG_CONFIG_HOME defined the config.toml file for Cointop would be placed into $XDG_CONFIG_HOME/.config/cointop/ rather than $XDG_CONFIG_HOME/cointop/.</description></item><item><title>Conveyor</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/projects/conveyor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 22:19:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://biehlerj.xyz/projects/conveyor/</guid><description>Conveyor is a series of frontend libraries for building an AutoInvent (which is a portmanteau of Automatic Inventory) application. It contains the following packages:
conveyor is a dashboard generator for inventory data conveyor-redux generates reducers and epics for use with conveyor conveyor-schema is a schema helper library for conveyor magql-query is a query builder and request tool for communicating with a magql backend My contributions to conveyor were mostly to conveyor and conveyor-redux.</description></item><item><title>Magql</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/projects/magql/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 22:20:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://biehlerj.xyz/projects/magql/</guid><description>Magql is a GraphQL framework for Python. It generates full-featured, customizable GraphQL API for your data.
My contributions to Magql was to automatically generate the proper primary key types from SQL to GraphQL.
You can find all my commits to magql on the GitHub page
Skills used:
Python Flask GraphQL</description></item></channel></rss>