<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Experience on Jacob Biehler</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/experience/</link><description>Recent content in Experience on Jacob Biehler</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://biehlerj.xyz/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Moebius Solutions</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/experience/moebius-solutions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://biehlerj.xyz/experience/moebius-solutions/</guid><description>December, 2019 to present Moebius Solutions, Inc. develops advanced Command and Control software, middleware, and integration platforms for the Navy and Marine Corps. Moebius Solutions has a focus on Opensource Culture and Technical Excellence.
I currently work at Moebius Solutions as a Jr. Software Engineer working for different customers. During my time at Moebius I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on the following:
Contributed to the AutoInvent projects Magql and Conveyor Worked on a desktop and mobile application with Electron and Flutter Worked on modernizing the customer infrastructure and deployment with OpenShift, Docker, and Jenkins Rewriting and adding new features to customer frontend using modern frontend practices and libraries like Typescript, React, and Redux Documented test procedures for the customer end users using LaTeX Created a Java class in existing code base to dynamically generate markdown with the status of an application and rendered the document in the browser using drawdown.</description></item><item><title>ScoreShuttle</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/experience/scoreshuttle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://biehlerj.xyz/experience/scoreshuttle/</guid><description>January, 2019 to May, 2019 ScoreShuttle is a service that helps manage credit and dispute management automatically. It helps users review their credit score, dispute credit inaccuracies, and protect credit data.
At ScoreShuttle I was a Jr. Software Engineer and worked on the following things:
Added new routes to the RESTful API for credit management services Created administrator tools to manage customer accounts, get sales data, and allow for 3rd parties to be added to the service Fixed a bug in the email template API to correctly format and send emails to customers Technologies used:</description></item></channel></rss>