<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Education on Jacob Biehler</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/education/</link><description>Recent content in Education on Jacob Biehler</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 22:35:58 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://biehlerj.xyz/education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Security Plus</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/education/certs/security-plus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 22:35:58 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://biehlerj.xyz/education/certs/security-plus/</guid><description>While working for Moebius Solutions I got my CompTIA Security+ certificate in order to certify my skills in cybersecurity.
You can find my Security+ certification on Credly.</description></item><item><title>Code School</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/education/code-school/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://biehlerj.xyz/education/code-school/</guid><description>Attended from: September, 2017 to December, 2019 Degree: N/A Location: San Francisco, CA At the coding school I attended in San Francisco I learned full stack software engineering. The curriculum covered shell scripting, systems programming with C, backend web development with Python, Flask, and MySQL, frontend web development with JavaScript and JQuery, and DevOps with Puppet, Python, uwsgi, and Nginx. The curriculum was project based with the final project culminating in building a full stack clone of Airbnb.</description></item><item><title>Mesa College</title><link>https://biehlerj.xyz/education/mesa-college/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://biehlerj.xyz/education/mesa-college/</guid><description>Attended from: August, 2012 to June, 2017 Degree: Associate&amp;rsquo;s Degree of Science in Business Administration Location: San Diego, CA At Mesa College I did general education for an undergraduate degree in Business Administration. I first got an Associate&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Economics when I decided to get an Associate&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Business Administration. During my time at Mesa College included learning some basic programming using Visual Basic.</description></item></channel></rss>